<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unconstrain your business potential on Kavin Lam</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unconstrain your business potential on Kavin Lam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deep Customer Alignment and Research</title>
      <link>/posts/deep-customer-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/deep-customer-alignment/</guid>
      <description>How well do you know your customer?&amp;hellip;.can you prove it? Do you have a strong understanding on the motivations and needs of your customers? Using the best methodologies of innovation, human centered design, and blending qualitative and quantitative data, we help clients gain market advantages through a 360 degree understanding of customer’s current and future needs. This allows us to design strategies and products that best fit your customer’s wants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation and Blue Sky Solutions</title>
      <link>/posts/language-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/language-perfect/</guid>
      <description>We can only build toward what we can imagine We refuse to be constrained by the current state of operation. Our strength is believing we can create anything we can imagine. To accomplish this, we take learnings across many industries, Blue Sky thinking workshops, and tapping into your whole organizations&amp;ndash;from the team members turning wrenches to senior leadership. Innovation comes from everywhere, we are here to help you capture that magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations and Strategy Consulting</title>
      <link>/posts/operations-and-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/operations-and-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Evolution As companies grow, operations need to evolve and be nimble to support changing needs. We take a holistic approach to understanding the operational system you have built, as well as the ecosystem of your suppliers, customers, competitors.
Streamline operations, supply chain, and process management to create a flexible organization. We are experts in aligning your business model with the right operational capabilities. By applying robust systems thinking and Theory of Constraints methodology, our process provides a roadmap to identifying the levers and constraints to exploit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>What we beleive in  These principles guide our realtionship with our clients and our work. The integrity of our work is why we do this.
 Honesty  Honesty is the foundation of success.  It is why our clients trust us, why our work is exemplary, and why we care about our product.
Continous Improvement Any business environment can become a system of continuous improvement  Any system can be designed or redesigned to welcome the changing dyanmics of any market or customer</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
